ZOENORDEN

CONTACT

970 - 692 - 3299

≥ znorden17@outlook.com

https://github.com/znorden

EDUCATION

Computer Science, BS

Montana State University Bozeman, MT | May 2022

China Studies, Minor

Montana State University Bozeman, MT | May 2022

LANGUAGES

C/C++, Python, Java, HTML/CSS, Javascript

SKILLS

Adobe Creative Cloud Suite, Linux systems, conversational Mandarin

PROJECTS

Seed Labs

Jan. 2021 - May 2021 Successfully demonstrated how vulnerabilities were exploited to gain root access to a system.

Home Security System

Oct. 2021 - PRESENT

Developed a mobile application
that receives alerts from a server
everytime a door is opened/closed.

PROFILE

My background involves living and traveling the world for most of my high school career and being able to experience several different unique cultures. These experiences have helped me to develop interpersonal and problem-solving skills, a high level of independence, good time management, flexibility, and the ability to work with people of different backgrounds.

EXPERIENCE

IT Intern

Lumibird | Bozeman, MT | Nov. 2021 - PRESENT

- Assist in getting this branch of Lumibird NIST SP 800-171 certified
- Assist 100+ workers with day-to-day technology problems

Teaching Assistant at Montana State University

Montana State University | Bozeman, MT | Jan. 2021 - PRESENT

- Communicated C to individuals with some computer science experience
- Communicated Python to individuals with no computer science experience.

Cyber Security Intern

Zoot INC. | Bozeman, MT | Dec. 2020

Researched phishing educational and tracking programs

Computer Science Help Center Volunteer

Montana State University | Bozeman, MT | Jan. 2021 - PRESENT

 Communicated many different programming languages and concepts to many individuals of a variety of different backgrounds.

AWARDS

Montana State University Dean's List

Montana State University | Bozeman, MT | Fall 2020, Spring 2021

Montana State University Grace Hopper Sponsorship Award

Montana State University | Bozeman, MT | 2019, 2021